A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of XX, XX-XX (bulk 2014-2017)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, XX-XX., Extent: XX-XX cubic feet (XX boxes). (Box X-X)
  - Conflict of interest, 2016. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Delegation meeting, 2014 Apr 9. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Congressional Delegation meeting, 2017 Mar 22. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Council of Virginia's Future - Highlights, 2014. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - CRM recurring themes, 2014-2015. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cross-border information sharing, 2014. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Death penalty - General, 2016. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Disability Services System in Virginia, Assessment of, 2014. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Domestic drones, undated. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Domestic Violence, 2014. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Domestic Violence Leave - Study request, 2015. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Drive-to-Work, 2015. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Ebola - Decision brief, 2014. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Election Modernization and Cybersecurity Efforts - Presentation, undated. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Electromagnetic Pulse Special Interest Group - Meeting, 2014 Sept 3. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Emergencies and Disasters - Planning activities, undated. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Action Plan, 2014. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Events and Media Coordination Overview, 2017 Apr 28. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Executive actions - Proposed, 2014. (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Executive agreements, 2014. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Executive agreements, 2016. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Executive clemency, 2014. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Executive Directive - Assessing Lesbian, Gay and Transgender Disparities in the Commonwealth (draft), 2015. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Executive Order 50 - Banning Guns in State Government Buildings, 2015. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Executive orders - Pending, 2014. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Executive Summary - Governor's Guide to Homeland Security, undated. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Exports - Notes, undated. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation - Civil Rights Program, undated. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency, 2014. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Financial statements, 2014. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Financial statements, 2015. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Financial statements, 2016. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Financial statements, 2017. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fishback Cases - Policy Problems and Responses (briefing), 2017 July 28. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs Security Training Center (FASTC), 2014 June. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 2014-2015. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Overvies, 2014. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - GeoGroup, 2014. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Gifts, 2014. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Governor McAuliffe: Three Years Expanding the New Virginia Economy, 2016. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Governor's 365 Day Report, 2015. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Blueprint for Workforce Development, 2015. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Fellows, 2014. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Strategic Priorities - Public Safety and Homeland Security, undated. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gun violence, 2014. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Guns, 2015. (Box 21, Folder 8a)
  - Health, Dept. of - Virginia Harm Reduction, undated. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - High Cost Prescription Drug Workgroup, 2016. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Homeland Security, U.S. Dept. of - Border Security and Immigration Enforcement, 2017. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - HUD / NDRC Grant update meeting, 2015 Sept 3. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Human trafficking - Legislation, 2016. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), 2014. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), 2017. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Implementation of New Protective Order legislation, 2016. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Industry Credentials - Short term classes, undated. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Interfaith Action for Human Rights (IAHR), 2017. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Interns, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Interoperability Program Update, 2017 Feb 24. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - James River Association, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Justice Policy Institute, 2013-2014. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Lethal injection, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Library of Virginia, undated. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - License plate readers, 2015. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lobbyists and Legislative Liaisons, 2016. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Medicaid fraud, undated. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Mental Health - California, undated. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Mental Health - Cases for presentation, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Mental health and guns, undated. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Mental Illness in Jails Report, 201. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Mentally Ill in Virginia Jails, Joint Task Force on - Final Report, 1984. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Montpelier Foundation - Professional Development for Law Enforcement Officials, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - National Alliance of Mental Illness, 2015. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - National Criminal Justice Association, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - National Digital States Survey, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - National Drug Control Strategy, 2014. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - National Instant Background Check (NICS), undated. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - North Carolina Innocence Inquiry Commission, 2014. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Notes - Miscellaneous, undated. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Office of the Attorney General, 2015. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - OpEd drafts, undated. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Opioids - Executive Directive 9, 2016. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Opioids - NEMA/ASTHO/GHSAC Joint Policy Workgroup meeting, 2017 Aug 2. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Opioids - Opioid Addiction Crisis Datathon, 2017. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Opioids - Report of the Health and Criminial Justice Data Committee, 2016. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Opioids - Reports and presentations, 2017. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Opioids - Technology Innovation for Public Safety (TIPS) grants, 2017. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Opioids - Unified Command Response, 2017. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Opioids - Vivitrol, 2016. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Pardon and Process, 2014. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Paris attack, 2015. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Past executive orders, 2012-2014. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Personnel, 2014-2015. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Petition - Kevin Snodgrass, 2017. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Police and Fire World Games - Fairfax, 2015. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Press releases and drafts, 2016, undated. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Pretrial Services, 2014-2015. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Pretrial Services in Virginia - Presentation by Virginia Crime Commission, 2017- Nov 29. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Prison Fellowship, undated. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Protective orders, 2016. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Public Safety - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2014 Sept 15. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Public Safety Agency organizational charts, 2016. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Public Safety and Homeland Security - Homeland Security Group restructuring plan (decision brief), 2015 Apr 17. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Public Safety Policy Transition Committee, undated. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Public Safety trainings, 2014-2015. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Recidivism rate - Press release and talking points, 2016 Dec 13. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Report on the Offender Population Forecasts (FY15-20), 2014 Oct 15. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Restorative Justice, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Review of Disaster Preparedness Planning in Virginia (JLARC), 2013. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Regional Center for the Investigation of Incidents of Sexual and Gender Based Violence, 2017. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Regional jails - Medicaid savings, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Regional meetings (DC, MD and VA), 2014. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Registered sex offenders, 2014. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Restoration of rights, 2014. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Richmond protests, 2017. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Safety Pillar (PSHS newsletter), 2015. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Secretariats, 2016. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Shoreline Resiliency Fund, 2016-2017. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Smart on Crimes Solutions - Executive summary, 2014 June 17. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Soering, Jens, undated. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Staff meetings, 2014 May-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Staff meetings, 2015 Jan-June. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Staff meetings, 2015 July-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Staff meetings, 2016 Jan-May. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Staff meetings, 2016 June-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Staff meetings, 2017. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Staffing, Structure, and Resource concerns, 2015. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - State and Local Conflict of Interest Act, 201. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - State Inspector General, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - State Managed Shelter Overview (DSS), 2014 Aug. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2014-2017. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Statewide Fire Prevention Code, 2016. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Statewide Interoperability Communications - SWIC/SPOC turnover outline, 2017 Oct 5. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Stategic priorities, 2015. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Student debt crisis, 2016. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Transition, 2017-2018. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Transition Council on Preparedness Report, 2013 Dec. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Unite the Right Rally (Charlottesville), 2017. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Courts, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - Public Safety Poll, undated. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - Wilder School of Government and Public Affairs, undated. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Drug Courts, 2012. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Hazardous Materials Preparedness Fund, undated. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Sexual and Domestic Violence Action Alliance, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Virginia State Crime Commission, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Tech Family Outreach Foundation, 2014. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Virginia's Current Budget Situation - Presentation to Governor's Fellows (Richard Brown, Sec. of Finance), 2014 July 8. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Year One - The New Virginia Economy, 2015. (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Zika Virus Disease - Situation Report, 2017 Apr 28. (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Series III. Budget, 2013-2017., Extent: XX cubic feet (XX box). (Box XX)
  XX
  - Budget (2014-2016) - General, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - General, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - General, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Agency budget requests, 2013-2014. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Agency budget requests, 2013-2014. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget documents, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Governor's budget, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Presentations, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget reductions, 2014-2015. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget reductions - ABC, 2014-2015. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget reductions - DCJS, 2014-2015. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget reductions - DFS, 201. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget reductions - DJJ, 201. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget reductions - VSP, 2014-2015. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - General, 2015. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - General, 2015. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Agency requests, 2015. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget bill and amendments, 2015. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Budget (2014-2016) - Budget bill notes and presentations, 2015. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - General, 2016. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - Budget review, 2016. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - Health budget items, 2016. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - Reductions, 2016. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - General, 2017. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - Budget priorities, 2017. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - Budget requests, 2017. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Budget (2016-2018) - HB 1500, chapter 836, 2017. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Budget (2018-2020) - Agency budget requests, 2017. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Budget (2018-2020) - Agency technology requests, 2017. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Budget (2018-2020) - Budget decision package, 2017. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Series IV. Events, 2014-2018., Extent: XX cubic feet (X box). (Box XX)
  - Virginia's Behavioral Health Services System - Justice involved individuals with behavioral health disorders (presentation - Cochran), 2014 Jan 15. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Spotsylvania County Sheriff's Office Annual Awards Ceremony - Talking points, 2014 Feb 28. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Campus Safety and Violence Prevention Forum, 2014 Mar 17-19. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Services Act Conference, 2014 Mar 24-25. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Center for School and Campus Safety (DCJS) - Threat Assessment Conference, 2014 Mar 31- Apr 2. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Loudoun County Crime Victims Rights Week, 2014 Apr. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Council of Virginia's Future - Orientation, 2014 Apr 1. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Crisis Intervention Teams - Awards ceremony, 2014 Apr 2. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Forensic Science Academy graduation, 2014 Apr 11. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Association of Community-Based Providers - Presentation (Cochran), 2014 May 9. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Tobacco Trafficking and Organized Crime in Virginia - Judicial Conference of Virginia, 2014 May 13. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Peace Week Service, 2014 May 13. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Assisting Families of Inmates - Annual meeting, 2014 May 22. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Juvenile Correctional Officers - Graduation Ceremony (DJJ), 2014 June 6. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Crisis Intervention Team Advisory Council, 2014 June 12. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - State Executive Council Retreat, 2014 June 20. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Governor's Commission on Parole Review - Talking points, 2014 July 20. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Pre-trial Symposium, 2014 July 24. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Henrico County Police Division - 58th Basic Academy Graduation Exercises, 2014 aug 7. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - JCO Recruitment event (DJJ), 2014 Aug 13. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Homeland Security Law Institute, 2014 Aug 21-22. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Local Government Attorneys Conference, 2014 Sept 8. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - National Day of Service and Remembrance / 9/11 Day Observance, 2014 Sept 11. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Sheriff's Association Conference, 2014 Sept 14-16. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Correctional Association - Training Institute, 2014 Sept 24-26. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Western Groundbreaking (DFS), 2014 Sept 28. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Heroin and Prescription Drug Summit, 2014 Oct 2. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Municipal League Conference, 2014 Oct 5-7. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Task Force on Combating Campus Sexual Violence - Talking points, 2014 Oct 9. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Fusion Center Leader Program, 2014 nov 17-21. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Public Safety Memorial, 2014 Dec 6. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Campaign Awards and Recognition Event, 2015 Mar 26. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - ABC Law Enforcement Expert Review Panel, 2015 May 4. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Public Safety Training Center, 2015 May 14. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Symposium on Homeland Security and Defense, 2015 May 18-19. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Adult State Responsible Inmate Realignment Workgroup, 2015 May 27. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Bon Air Correctional Center - Tour, 2015 July 23. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Freedom of Information Advisory Council - Records Subcommittee, 2015 Aug 18. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Mathews County YMCA Emergency Shelter, 2015 Aug 21. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Weather event (WRVA) - Talking points, 2015 Oct 2. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Pilot - Interview, 2015 Oct 16. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Criminal Justice Reform Panel Discussion - White House, 2015 Oct 22. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Janie Porter Barrett Commemorative Event (DJJ), 2015 Oct 28. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Criminal Sentencing Commission, 2015 Nov 10. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Council of Governors - Conference call, 2015 Dec 15. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Statewide Communication Interoperability Plan (SCIP) and Governance Briefing, 2016 Jan 28. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Council of Governors, 2016 Feb 19. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Recovery Summit, 2016 Feb 27. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Fire Chiefs Association Conference, 2016 Feb 27. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Sheriffs' Association, 2016 Mar 17. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Physical Evidence Recovery Kit (PERK) bill signing, 2016 Apr 14. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Law Enforcement Memorial - Talking points, 2016 May 3. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - CVS Pharmacy / Naloxone Press Conference, 2016 May 11. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - Wilder School of Government and Public Affairs, 2016 May 14. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Community Criminal Justice Association - Talking points, 2016 May 20. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Alexandria Probation and Parole Office - Talking points, 2016 May 24. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Promotion ceremony, 2016 June 6. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Heroin Response Stragegy Symposium, 2016 June 22-23. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Association of Commonwealth's Attorneys - Annual Summer Conference, 2016 Aug 4-7. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Annual (12th) Virginia Transportation Stakeholders Fall Legislative Roundtable, 2016 Oct 11. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Coastal Policy Center Annual Conference, 2016 Dec 2. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Governing Magazine - Virginia Leadership Conference, 2016 Dec 9. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Coffee and Conversation with Secretary Moran, 2016 Dec 9. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - VEST / Homeland Security and Resilience Group, 2017 Mar 28. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Data Analytics Summit (Pre-Summit event), 2017 Apr 10. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Hurricane Matthew - Recovery and Resilience discussion with Hampton Roads Stakeholders, 2017 Apr 13. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - VAS and Drone briefing, 2017 May 31. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Combating the Opioid Crisis - Testimony before the U.S. House Committee of Energy and Commerce, Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations, 2017 July 12. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Resilient Virginia Conference, 2017 Aug 1-2. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Bon Air Family Day, 2017 Aug 27. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Youth Lunch (DJJ), 2017 Aug 27. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Regional Meeting (DC/MD/VA), 2017 Aug 28. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Virginia-Maryland College of Veterinary Medicine - External Advisory Board/Public Health Program, 2017 Oct 16. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Virginia National Guard - 116th return from U.S. Virgin Islands, 2017 Oct 17. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Revive Virginia - Talking points, 2017. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Coastal Policy Center Conference, Defending Our Coasts - Talking points, 2017 Oct 27. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Governor McAuliffe's Millennial Civic Engagement Forum, 2017 Oct 27. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Women's Monument groundbreaking ceremony, 2017 Dec 4. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Winter storm briefing - Talking points, 2018 Jan 3. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Management Awareness Group, undated. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Fairfax County Criminal Justice Academy Graduation, undated. (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Freedom of Information Act - Talking points, undated. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - House Appropriation briefing, undated. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - National Coalition of Public Safety Officers - Talking points, undated. (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Senate Finance briefing, undated. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Municipal League Conference, undated. (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Virginia's Homeland Security presentation, undated. (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Series V. Governor's Decision Requests, 2014, 2016-2018., Extent: X cubic feet (X box). (Box XX)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Decision Requests - Corrections, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2016 Jan. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2016 June-July. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2016 Aug-Sept. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2016 Oct-Dec. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2017 Feb-Mar. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2017 May-Aug. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2017 Sept-OCt. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2017 Dec. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2018 Jan. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Hiring Requests - ABC, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Hiring Requests - DOC, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Hiring Requests - DOC, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Hiring Requests - DCJS, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Hiring Requests - VDEM, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Hiring Requests - DFP, 201. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Hiring Requests - DFS, 201. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Hiring Requests - DJJ, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Hiring Requests - DMA, 201. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Hiring Requests - Parole Board, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Hiring Requests - VSP, 2014. (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Series V. Legislative Files, 2014-2018., Extent: X cubic feet (X box). (Box XX)
  The Legislative Files series is housed in X boxes and are arranged chronologically. This series consists of legislation and supporting documentation affecting the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, as well as state agencies assigned to the Secretariat. This series needs to be reviewed for confidential information before being served to public.
  - Legislation - 2014 General Assembly Session
    - Legislation, 2014. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Enrolled bill review, 2014. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Legislative procedures, 2014. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Potential legislation, 2014. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Legislation - 2015 General Assembly Session
    - Legislation, 2015. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Campus sexual violence, 2015. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Enrolled bill review, 2015. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - HB 1427 - Felony homicide, 2015. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - HB 1458 - Naloxone, 2015. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - HB 1673 - Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act, 2015. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - HB 1702 - Voluntary background checks, 2015. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - HB 1749/HB 1770 - Expungement of protective orders, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 2125 - Unmanned aircraft systems, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 2286 - Posession of firearms by convicted felons, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 2321 - 20 week bill, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HJR 622 Alternative sentencing, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HR 214 Personhood, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - SB 733 and HB 1524 Ultrasound repeal, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - SB 772 and HB 1823 Equal pay, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - SB 990 and HB 1945 Domestic violence leave, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - SB 1032 Virginia Alcoholic Beverage Control Authority, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - SB 1193 Academic transcripts, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - SB 1195 Special Conservators of the Peace, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - SB 1211 and HB 1600 Marriage equality, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - SB 1269 Distilleries, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - SB 1301 Unmanned aircraft systems, 2015. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Legislation, 2016.
  - Gun legislation, 2016.
  - HB 143 Neutral grain spirits, 2016.
  - HB 903 Commonwealth Center for Recurrent Flooding Resiliency, 2016.
  - HB 1213 Blueprint for Change / Education, 2016.
  - SB 291 Physical Evidence Recovery Kits (PERK), 2016.